A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1942
  - West Indies, 1942; 1942/431
    - West Indies - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/431.E
      - Windward Islands, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
  - Bahamas, 1942; 1942/433
    - Bahamas - Health Services, 1942; 1942/433.K
      - FOX-1 Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Survey of Nassau, New Providence Island, Bahamas", 1942 (Box 561, Folder 3818)
  - Jamaica, 1942; 1942/437
    - Jamaica, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
    - Jamaica - Nursing, 1942; 1942/437.C
      - Jamaica, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
  - Trinidad, 1942; 1942/451
    - Trinidad, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
  - Windward Islands, 1942; 1942/455
    Windward Islands
    - Windward Islands, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
  - St. Lucia, 1942; 1942/457
    - St. Lucia - Public Health Education, 1942; 02.1942/457.L
      - St. Lucia, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)
  - India, 1942; 1942/464
    - India - Administration, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1657)
    - India - (A-Z), 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1658)
    - India - Nursing, 1942; 1942/464.C
      - India, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/464.L
      - India, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1942; 1942/464.O
      - India, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/464.S
      - India, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - India (Mysore), 1942; 1942/464.1
      - Mysore, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - India (Travancore), 1942; 1942/464.5
      - Tranvancore, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
  - Iraq, 1942; 1942/470
    - Iraq, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1942; 1942/470.I
      - Iraq, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
  - Africa, 1942; 1942/475
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/475.S
      - Africa, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1659)
  - East Africa, 1942; 1942/477
    - FOX Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Surveys - East Africa", 1942 (Box 561, Folder 3819)
  - North Africa Region, 1942; 1942/485
    - Egypt, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1660)
    - North Africa Region - Hookworm, 1942; 1942/485.H
      - Annual Report, Bilharzia, Snail Destruction Section - AR-2 - (1942) 1946 (Box 561, Folder 3820)
  - South Africa, 1942; 1942/487
    - South Africa, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1660)
  - West Africa, 1942; 1942/495
    Africa, Central
    - BEL - FOX Fox, Leon A. "Belgian Congo - Sanitary Surveys", 1942 (Box 561, Folder 3821)
    - FRE - FOX Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Survey of Pointe Noire, French Equatorial Africa", 1942 (Box 562, Folder 3822)
  - France, 1942; 1942/500
    - France - (A-R), 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1660)
    - France - (S-Z), 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1661)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/500.A
      - France, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1661)
  - Society Islands, 1942; 1942/520
    Scope and Contents note
    Inclues Tahiti.
    French Polynesia
    - Tahiti, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1661)
  - French West Africa, 1942; 1942/521
    - Equatorial Africa, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1661)
  - China, 1942; 1942/601
    - China (A-H), 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1662)
    - China (H-P), 1942 (Box 240, Folder 1663)
    - China (P-Z), 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/601.A
      - China, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - China - Nursing, 1942; 1942/601.C
      - China, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/601.E
      - China, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - China - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/601.L
      - China, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/601.R
      - China, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
  - Japan, 1942; 1942/609
    - Japan, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1942; 1942/650
    - Netherlands, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1664)
  - Europe, 1942; 1942/700
    - Europe, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
  - Austria, 1942; 1942/705
    - Austria, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
  - Belgium, 1942; 1942/707
    - Belgium, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/707.R
      - Belgium, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
  - Zaire, 1942; 1942/709
    - Zaire, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
  - Yugoslavia, 1942; 1942/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1665)
  - Bulgaria, 1942; 1942/711
    - Bulgaria, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1942; 1942/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Estonia, 1942; 1942/714
    - Estonia, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Iceland, 1942; 1942/715
    Iceland
    - STR-1 Strode, George K. "A Survey of Iceland", 1942 (Box 562, Folder 3823)
  - Germany, 1942; 1942/717
    - Germany, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Hungary, 1942; 1942/750
    - Hungary, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Italy, 1942; 1942/751
    - Italy, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1666)
  - Liberia, 1942; 1942/759
    Liberia
    - Liberia - Health Services, 1942; 1942/759.K
      - FOX-1 Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Survey of Liberia", 1942 (Box 562, Folder 3824)
  - Norway, 1942; 1942/767
    - Norway, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/767.A
      - Norway, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/767.E
      - Norway, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
  - Iran, 1942; 1942/771
    - Iran, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
    - Iran - Malaria, 1942; 1942/771.I
      - Iran, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
  - U.S.S.R., 1942; 1942/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
    - U.S.S.R. - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/785.R
      - U.S.S.R., 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
  - Finland, 1942; 1942/787
    - Finland, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1667)
  - Poland, 1942; 1942/789
    - Poland, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/789.A
      - Poland, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Spain, 1942; 1942/795
    Spain
    - Spain, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Switzerland, 1942; 1942/803
    - Switzerland, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Near East Region, 1942; 1942/804
    Middle East
    - Near East, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Turkey, 1942; 1942/805
    - Turkey, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Cyprus, 1942; 1942/809
    - Cyprus, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Palestine, 1942; 1942/833
    - Palestine, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
  - Trustees, 1942; 1942/903
    - Trustees, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1668)
- General Correspondence, 1943
  - International, 1943; 1943/100
    - (A-F), 1943 (Box 241, Folder 1669)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1943 (Box 241, Folder 1670)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1671)
    - (F-L), 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1672)
    - (L-M), 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1673)
    - Nutrition, 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1674)
    - (O-P), 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1675)
    - (Q-U), 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1676)
    - War - Health Problems, 1943 (Box 242, Folder 1677)
    - W-Z, 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1678)
    - International - Nursing, 1943; 1943/100.C
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1679)
    - International - Malaria, 1943; 1943/100.I
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1679)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1943; 1943/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1679)
      - SOP Soper, Fred L. "The Organization of Permanent Nationwide Anti-Aedes Aegypti Measures in Brazil", 1943 (Box 562, Folder 3824a)
  - United States, 1943; 1943/200
    - United States - (A-Al), 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1680)
    - United States - (American A-I), 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1681)
    - United States - (American L-R), 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1682)
    - United States - (American S-Az), 1943 (Box 243, Folder 1683)
    - United States - (B-Bl), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1684)
    - United States - (Bo-Bz), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1685)
    - United States - (C-Ci), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1686)
    - United States - (Cl-Co), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1687)
    - United States - (Co), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1688)
    - United States - (Co-Ez), 1943 (Box 244, Folder 1689)
    - United States - (F), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1690)
    - United States - (G-Ha), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1691)
    - United States - Harvard - (A-G), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1692)
    - United States - Harvard - (H-Z), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1693)
    - United States - Harvard - (Ha-Hz), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1694)
    - United States - (I-In), 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1695)
    - United States - (In-Kz), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1696)
    - United States - (L), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1697)
    - United States - (M-Me), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1698)
    - United States - (Mi-Na), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1699)
    - United States - (Na-Nz), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1700)
    - United States - (O-Po), 1943 (Box 246, Folder 1701)
    - United States - (Po-Re), 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1702)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars, 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1703)
    - United States - (Re-Rz), 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1704)
    - United States - (Sa-Sn), 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1705)
    - United States - (So-Un), 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1706)
    - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration - Health, 1943 (Box 247, Folder 1707)
    - United States - (U.S. - A-E), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1708)
    - United States - (U.S. - H-Public Health Service), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1709)
    - United States - (U.S. - Public Health Service - Z), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1710)
    - United States - (Un-V), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1711)
    - United States - (W), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1712)
    - United States - (X-Z), 1943 (Box 248, Folder 1713)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/200.A
      - United States - General Medical Council, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1714)
      - United States - General Medical Council, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1715)
      - United States - Medical Education, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1716)
      - United States - Medical Education - Medical Research - Middlesex College, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1716)
      - United States - National Research Council, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1717)
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1718)
    - United States - Nursing, 1943; 1943/200.C
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1718)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/200.E
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1718)
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1719)
    - United States - Declinations, 1943; 1943/200.F
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1719)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1943; 1943/200.L
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1719)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/200.R
      - United States, 1943 (Box 249, Folder 1719)
      - United States - (M-R), 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1720)
      - United States - Regional Studies, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1721)
      - United States - (S-Z), 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1722)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/200.S
      - United States - (A-S), 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1723)
      - United States - (T-Z), 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1724)
  - Arkansas, 1943; 1943/204
    - Arkansas, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1725)
  - California, 1943; 1943/205
    - California, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1725)
    - California - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/205.R
      - California, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1726)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/205.S
      - California, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1726)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1943; 1943/206
    - Panama Canal Zone - Malaria, 1943; 1943/206.I
      - Canal Zone, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1726)
  - Colorado, 1943; 1943/207
    - Colorado, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1726)
  - Connecticut, 1943; 1943/208
    - Connecticut, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1727)
  - Florida, 1943; 1943/211
    - Florida, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1727)
    - Florida - Yellow Fever, 1943; 1943/211.O
      - Florida, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1727)
  - Georgia, 1943; 1943/212
    - Georgia, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1727)
    - Georgia - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/212.A
      - Georgia, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1727)
  - Hawaii, 1943; 1943/214
    - Hawaii, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Illinois, 1943; 1943/216
    - Illinois, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Kentucky, 1943; 1943/220
    - Kentucky, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Louisiana, 1943; 1943/221
    - Louisiana, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Maine, 1943; 1943/222
    - Maine, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Maryland, 1943; 1943/223
    - Maryland, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1728)
  - Massachusetts, 1943; 1943/224
    - Massachusetts, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1729)
    - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/224.A
      - Massachusetts, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1729)
  - Mississippi, 1943; 1943/227
    - Mississippi, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1729)
  - Nebraska, 1943; 1943/230
    - Nebraska, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1729)
  - New Hampshire, 1943; 1943/232
    - New Hampshire, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1729)
  - New Jersey, 1943; 1943/233
    - New Jersey, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1730)
  - New Mexico, 1943; 1943/234
    - New Mexico, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1730)
  - New York, 1943; 1943/235
    - New York, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1730)
  - North Carolina, 1943; 1943/236
    - North Carolina, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1730)
  - Ohio, 1943; 1943/238
    - Ohio, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
    - Ohio - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/238.R
      - Ohio, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
  - Oregon, 1943; 1943/240
    - Oregan, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
  - Pennsylvania, 1943; 1943/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
    - Pennsylvania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/241.E
      - Pennsylvania, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
    - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/241.R
      - Pennsylvania, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1731)
  - Philippines, 1943; 1943/242
    - Philippines, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1732)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/242.E
      - Philippines, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1732)
  - Rhode Island, 1943; 1943/244
    - Rhode Island, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1732)
  - South Carolina, 1943; 1943/246
    - South Carolina - Malaria, 1943; 1943/246.I
      - South Carolina (Box 251, Folder 1732)
  - Tennessee, 1943; 1943/248
    - Tennessee, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1732)
    - Tennessee - TVA, 1943 (Box 251, Folder 1733)
  - Virginia, 1943; 1943/252
    - Virginia, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
  - Washington, 1943; 1943/253
    - Washington, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
  - West Virginia, 1943; 1943/254
    - West Virginia, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
  - Wisconsin, 1943; 1943/255
    - Wisconsin, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
  - Virgin Islands, 1943; 1943/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
  - South America, 1943; 1943/300
    - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1734)
    - South America - Administration, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1735)
    - South America - Administration, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1736)
    - South America - Administration, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1737)
    - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1738)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/300.A
      - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1738)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/300.D
      - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1738)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/300.E
      - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1739)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/300.S
      - South America, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1739)
  - Argentina, 1943; 1943/301
    - Argentina, 1943 (Box 252, Folder 1740)
    - Argentina, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1741)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1943; 1943/301.C
      - Argentina, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/301.E
      - Argentina, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Argentina - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/301.S
      - Argentina, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
  - Bolivia, 1943; 1943/303
    - Bolivia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Bolivia - Nursing, 1943; 1943/303.C
      - Bolivia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943/303.E
      - Bolivia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Bolivia - Social Sciences, 1943/303.S (Box 253, Folder 1742)
      - Bolivia
  - Brazil, 1943; 1943/305
    - Brazil, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1943; 1943/305.C
      - Brazil, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1742)
  - Chile, 1943; 1943/309
    - Chile, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1743)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/309.A
      - Chile, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1743)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/309.E
      - Chile, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1743)
    - Chile - Respiratory Diseases, 1943; 1943/309.M
      - Chile, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1743)
    - Chile - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/309.S
      - Chile, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1743)
  - Colombia, 1943; 1943/311
    - Colombia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/311.A
      - Colombia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/311.D
      - Colombia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/311.S
      - Colombia, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
  - Costa Rica, 1943; 1943/313
    - Costa Rica, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/313.E
      - Costa Rica, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
  - Cuba, 1943; 1943/315
    - Cuba - (A-H), 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1744)
    - Cuba - (I-Z), 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
    - Cuba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/315.E
      - Cuba, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
  - Ecuador, 1943; 1943/317
    - Ecuador, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
  - Guatemala, 1943; 1943/319
    - Guatemala, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/319.D
      - Guatemala, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
  - Honduras, 1943; 1943/321
    - Honduras, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1745)
  - Mexico, 1943; 1943/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1746)
    - Mexico - (A-H), 1943 (Box 253, Folder 1747)
    - Mexico - (I-Z), 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1748)
    - Mexico - Nursing, 1943; 1943/323.C
      - Mexico - (I-Z), 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/323.D
      - Mexico, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/323.E
      - Mexico, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
    - Mexico - Public Health Education, 1943; 1943/323.L
      - Mexico, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/323.R
      - Mexico, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/323.S
      - Mexico, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1749)
  - Nicaragua, 1943; 1943/325
    - Nicaragua, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
    - Nicaragua - Malaria, 1943; 1943/325.I
      - Nicaragua, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
  - Panama, 1943; 1943/327
    - Panama, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
    - Panama - Malaria, 1943; 1943/327.I
      - Panama, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
    - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/327.R
      - Panama, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
  - Paraguay, 1943; 1943/329
    - Paraguay, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
    - Paraguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/329.E
      - Paraguay, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1750)
  - Peru, 1943; 1943/331
    - Peru, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1751)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/331.A
      - Peru, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/331.D
      - Peru, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/331.E
      - Peru, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
    - Peru - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/331.S
      - Peru, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
  - El Salvador, 1943; 1943/333
    - El Salvador, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
  - Dominican Republic, 1943; 1943/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
  - Uruguay, 1943; 1943/337
    - Uruguay, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
    - Uruguay - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/337.S
      - Uruguay, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1752)
  - Venezuela, 1943; 1943/339
    - Venezuela, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1753)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/339.D
      - Venezuela, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1753)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1753)
  - Great Britain, 1943; 1943/400
    - Great Britain, 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1753)
  - England, 1943; 1943/401
    - England - (E-H), 1943 (Box 254, Folder 1754)
    - England - (I-S), 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1755)
    - England - (T-Z), 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/401.A
      - England, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1943; 1943/401.D
      - England, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/401.E
      - England, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/401.R
      - England, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1943; 1943/401.S
      - England, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1756)
  - Scotland, 1943; 1943/405
    - Scotland, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1757)
  - Malta, 1943; 1943/409
    Malta
    - Malta, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1757)
  - Australia, 1943; 1943/410
    - Australia, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1757)
    - Australia, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1757)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/410.R
      - Australia, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1757)
  - Cook Islands, 1943; 1943/417
    - Cook Islands, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - New Zealand, 1943; 1943/418
    - New Zealand, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - Fiji, 1943; 1943/419
    - Fiji - Public Health Demonstrations, 1943; 1943/419.J
      - Fiji, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - Caribbean Region, 1943; 1943/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - Guyana, 1943; 1943/423
    - Guiana, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
    - Guyana - Tuberculosis, 1943; 1943/423.T
      - Guiana, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - Honduras, 1943; 1943/425
    - Honduras, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1758)
  - Canada, 1943; 1943/427
    - Canada - (A-C), 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1759)
    - Canada - (D-N), 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1760)
    - Canada - (O-Z), 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1761)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1943; 1943/427.A
      - Canada, 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1762)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1943; 1943/427.C
      - Canada, 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1762)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1943; 1943/427.E
      - Canada, 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1762)
    - Canada - Declinations, 1943; 1943/427.F
      - Canada - (A-F), 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1763)
      - Canada - (G-Z), 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1764)
    - Canada - Respiratory Diseases, 1943; 1943/427.M
      - Canada, 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1765)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1943; 1943/427.R
      - Canada, 1943 (Box 256, Folder 1765)